{
  "name": "Stranger Things",
  "color": [165,0,0],
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "question": "Who went in the upside down first",
      "answers": ["Will","Joyce","Mike","El"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Sheriff ?",
      "answers": ["Hopper","Karen","Ted","Joyce"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who died in the second episode",
      "answers": ["Barb","Will","Billy","Max"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who has the highest score on DigDug",
      "answers": ["Max","Will","Lucas","Dustin"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What are mornings for?",
      "answers": ["Coffee & Contemplation","Solving Crimes","Sloving Muders","Contemplating Donuts"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Joyce Byers",
      "answers": ["Will's Mom","Barb's Mom", "Max's Mom","Mike's Mom"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Papa's Name",
      "answers": ["Brenner","Brennan","Brandon","Brandan"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Vecna",
      "answers": ["Henry","Harrold","Harry","Hairy"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How did El visit her mom",
      "answers": ["Big Truck","Big Bus","Big Train","Big Car"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did Bob Die",
      "answers": ["The Lab","The Library","The Radio Shack","Byers's Home"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kelly's Number",
      "answers": ["008","002","011","010"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What the name of the test at the Lab",
      "answers": ["MKUltra","LKUltra","LXMega","LSMega"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Will say when asked who is Joyce",
      "answers": ["You're Mom","","LXMega","LSMega"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Dimension",
      "answers": ["The Upside Down","The Rightside Up","The Flippedside Down","The Downside Up"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Arcade",
      "answers": ["The Palace Arcade","The Strange Arcade","The Retro Arcade","The Cyber Arcade"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was Will's body found",
      "answers": ["The Quarry","Lover's Lake","Mirkwood","Benny's Burger"],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
}